How do you people in Crimea feel about the fact
Как вы люди в Крыму относитесь к тому
that it could be like with Kherson, that it could
что может быть как с херсоном что может
return back to
вернуться назад в
Ukraine, listen to you, the militia
Украину слушайте вам 8 лет ополчение
gave it to Crimea for 8 years and they didn’t even have time to enter, two
давало в Крым так и не успели зайти два
wagons arrived with weapons for the Crimean Tatars, they gave them weapons, they
вагона приехало крымским татарам с
turned around, they left back,
оружием дали развернулись уехали обратно
two wagons with weapons, and you don’t know,
два вагона с оружием А вы не в курсе да
no, tell me,
нене расскажите
Hello, where are you from in the
зст Здравствуйте
great Russian city of
держа с великого русского города
Sevastopol now,
Севастополя сейчас
where is it in the great Russian city of Sevastopol, it’s
где в Великом русском городе Севастополь
cool, listen, explain this to me,
прикольно слушайте объясните мне такой
everything flows, it changes, here was
вот всё такое течёт меняется Вот был
Sevastopol in Ukraine, then Russia
Севастополь в Украине потом Росси
in Sevastopol, what’s there, some
ди Севастополе что там Бут какие-то
Right Sector, and so on,
правый сектор и так
Sevastopol, Right Sector, Well, like, aren’t
да Севастополе Правый сектор Ну типа не
you afraid, yes, that some
боитесь Вы да что придут какие-то
Banderites will come, and so on
бандеровцы И так
[music]
[музыка]
further, personally, I’m not
дальше Лично я я не
afraid, That is, in principle, people will
боюсь То есть в принципе люди нормально
accept it normally if the Russian army leaves
воспримут если Российская армия уйдёт
like it left Kherson, if it leaves
как ушла из Херсона если уйдёт из
Sevastopol,
Севастополя
compare
Сравните
pam, both are included in the Constitution of the Russian
пам и то и то в Конституцию Российской
Federation as  region and
Федерации вписан как регион и
everything Well, Kherson region Yes, it is included in
всё Ну Херсонская область Да вписана
the Constitution of the Russian Federation, they
Конституцию Российской Федерации вот из
left Kherson and also Crimea is included, they
Херсона ушли и также Крым вписан из
can
Крыма могут
leave Crimea
уйти
Well, if, for example, Russia refuses to
Ну если допустим Россия откажется
leave the Basfor Dardanelles, then maybe it is
от выхода басфор дарданелла тогда может
worth talking about this, but it is unlikely that
быть об этом стоит поговорить но навряд
Russia will refuse this,
ли Россия в это от этого откажется Тем
Especially when the Americans buy oil
более когда Американцы покупают нефть
through
через
[music]
[музыка]
no Well, look, we cannot make any
не Ну смотри мы не можем ничего
predictions, look, Anything is possible, maybe
загадывать смотри Всё может быть может
Russia can capture Kyiv and Lvov And
Россия может захватить Киев да и Львов А
maybe Russia will leave Crimea Donetsk needs
может Россия уйдёт из Крыма Донец нужен
your ki and yours Look, I am not saying that it
твой ки и твой Смотри Я я не говорю что
will be Yes, everything changes in this world Everything
будет Да всё меняется в этом мире Всё
can change Yes, today, but tomorrow
может меняться Да сегодня но завтра
Russia can reach Berlin again,
может Россия дойти до Берлина снова да
yes, you started from the wrong place, so Tomorrow
да ты начал не оттуда так вот Завтра
Crimea may return Donetsk Lugansk
может там вернуться Крым Донецк Луганск
back to Ukraine How are you people in a
назад в Украину Как вы люди в
dream,
сном
maybe for 8 years the militia gave in to Crimea and did
может 8 лет ополчение давало в Крым так
not have time to enter, two wagons arrived
и не успели зайти два вагона приехала
Crimea Tata with weapons turned back
Крым Тата с оружием развернулись обратно
wagons with weapons And in the know,
вагона с оружием А в курсе дажи
such information was even received that I am
поступила такая информация что я
here two wagons What
тут два вагона Это в каком
year is this  whose year th year what date
году это чей год тый год какой дата
approximately it was spring was closer to
приблизительно это весна было ближе к
winter It's
зиме Это
probably the end of
наверно конец
February Well approximately
февраля Ну приблизительно
from the twenties To the twenty-ninth That's how it is
от двадцатых До двадцать девятого числа
let's remember Let's So what does it
Вот так вот давайте так пом Давайте Так
mean information came that
и что значит пришла информация что едут
wagons with weapons are coming yes these were
вагоны с оружием так да это вагоны
freight wagons passenger passenger
товарные были пассажирские пассажирский
as I
так
understood
понял
Sevastopol no to Simferopol that is no
Севастополь нет в Симферополь а то есть
longer in Sevastopol to Simferopol understood
уже не в Севастополя в Симферополь понял
you were in Simferopol And who told you
вы были в Симферополе А кто вам говорил
that in Sevastopol understood you were in
что в Севастополе понял вы тогда были в
Simferopol then yes
Симферополе да
I was in Simferopol then so good
я тогда был Симферополе так хорошо
further Tell me
дальше Расскажите
interesting well the wagons didn't arrive And where did they
интересно ну не доехали вагоны А где они
stop in my opinion
остановились по-моему
what is the village
как э деревня
called Proguli I don't remember the village
называется прогули я не вспомню деревню
name no And maybe someone saw these
название не А может и кто-то видел эти
wagons somewhere video of these wagons with
вагоны где-то видео этих вагонов с
weapons because you yes yes you can You
оружием потому что вы да да вы може Вы
can find all this on the Internet in the
можете найти всё это в интернете в
public domain le Tell me tell me where
открытом доступе ле Скажите скажите где
Find and tell me now I'll open it
Найдите и скажите я тоже сейчас открою
on YouTube you can find so really
на Ютюбе можете найти так вот реально
look at me now watching  2,000
смотрите у меня сейчас смотрит 2.000
viewers we will now finally show
зрителей мы сейчас покажем наконец-то
these in short wagons with weapons Let's
эти короче вагоны с оружием Давайте
Tell you on YouTube we need to find Yes yes
Скажите вам на Ютюбе найти надо Да да
these wagons with weapons SMU I'm
эти вагоны с оружием СМУ Мне же
interested
интересно
let me show you now well really
давайте я бы сейчас показал ну реально
maybe they hid this from us there are a
может от нас скрывали
lot of you What is
это вас много Что
hiding
скрывает
damn and there they directly show this weapon
блин и там прямо показывают это оружие
unloading and people right sectors Who who was
выгружает и людей право секторы Кто кто
carrying this weapon
Вёз это оружие
and why did you meet at the station you
а зачем вы на вокзале встречали вы
wanted to unload this I can't understand
хотели типа выгружать это не могу понять
no they
нет
wanted people with weapons there a whole wagon of
хотели там люди с оружием целый вагон
weapons and they wanted to give And what do you think
оружия а хотели дать А вы что думаете
that the EU with weapons then people were
что ЕС с оружием то люди
going to be like oh we'll see
собирались такие типа ой мы увидим
wagons traveling with weapons and I just simply
вагоны едут с оружием и я просто просто
never rode in wagons with weapons and
никогда не ехал в вагонах с оружием и
never met wagons with weapons I'm
никогда не встречал вагоны с оружием Мне
interested in how this happens there are
интересно как это происходит там едет
wagons full of weapons traveling and men with weapons
полные вагоны оружия и мужики с оружием
and then just boys come out to wave to the
а там выходят просто пацанчики помахать
date
дате
I want to show all
Я прямо сейчас хочу чтоб показать всем
my viewers right now I'm
своим зрителям мне ж интересно
really interested Is there a telegram or
действительно А есть в телеграме или
somewhere else where I can send you a link
где-нибудь ещё где вам ссылочку скинуть
like this in Utah
можно так в Юту
Tell me the name of the video I'll open it right now for
Скажите название видео Я сейчас открою
you by the way how old are you
прям вам кстати сколько лет
now I'm 33 33
сейчас мне 33 33
got it And how old are you
понял А вам сколько лет
43 43 you were 20 years old not How many 19
43 43 это вам было 20 лет не Сколь 19
years old Yes
лет Да
it would be plus minus 19
было это бы плю мину 19
cool damn it's just a Tarantino
прикольно блин это прям тарантиновские
movie - a nine-year-old boy goes to the
фильм-то девятилетний парень идёт в
Simferopol train station to give it to the men
Симферополь на вокзал давать мужикам
who are carrying a full train car of weapons it's
которые везут полный вагон оружия это
just an
прям
action movie I would have
боевик мне
already been on the Internet just everywhere
было бы уже в интернете просто везде
everywhere Now wait I'm turning on I
всюду Сейчас подожди
mean VPN And why do you need
включаю В смысле VPN А для чего Вам
VPN Well, YouTube
VPN Ну у нас же YouTube
slows down for us You
замедляет You у вас
slow down for you in
замедляют в
Find in
Найдите в
vat
вате
with yes for you with or
с да вам с пином или
without pin Let's try In the tube
без Давайте попробуем В тубе найти у
I already find People are shouting Come on come on a video with
меня уже Люди кричат Давай давай видос с
eat weapons
поест оружие
by the way the date is February 20th seven if anything so
кстати дата дцать сед февраля если что
she By the way she is on youtube yes
так она Кстати она юбе есть да
your subscribers
там ваших подписчиков
work there or whoever is there Where are you streaming On
работает или кто там Вы где стрими На
twitch or where In the
твиче или где В
tube youtube
тубе юбе
streams don't keep our interest coming on already
стрими не томи наш интерес давай уже
a video Damn come on damn We want it like that I build up
видос Блин давай блин Мы хотим так я
the intrigue will you turn on I know this
интригу нагнетай включишь я знаю этот
joke no wait
прикол нет подожди
[music]
[музыка]
Yes, yes, this is a guy from Sevastopol. He will
Да да это парень из Севастополя Нам
now show us a video of a
сейчас покажет видео как в Симферополь
train with weapons going to Simferopol in what year. They
шёл в чем году поезд с оружием Да его
stopped it there at some point. They called it the Friendship train. This is a
там остановили в какой-то его назвали ещ
real sensation. It will be a sensation
поз Дружбы это реально сенсация будет
now, people. This is a
сечас народ это сенсация это поезд
friendship train. How did the friendship train go in the day? This is a
дружбы как в дено поез дружбы это позд
real sensation with weapons. You know, they hid this information from us.
реально с оружием понимаете от нас
Turchinov, Poroshenko, Zelensky.
скрывали турчинов Порошенко Зеленский
And now, finally, my
эту информацию и я сейчас наконец-то мой
channel will explode and it will be shorter. A
канал сейчас взорвётся и будет короче
bomb, a rocket. I will be the first to show it. Trump Trump.
бомба ракета я первый покажу Трамп Трамп
That's all you're telling there. The
Это всё что ты там рассказываешь вот
Friendship train is finally here. I have achieved
поезд Дружбы есть наконец-то Я пришёл к
success. I have achieved success. I will be the first to
успеху Я пришёл к успеху я сейчас первый
show a sensation to a wide audience.
кто покажу сенсацию на широкую аудиторию
So, I'm already getting ready. Come on, Masik's last name
так Я уже готовлюсь Давай фамилия Масик
tells you something about Mac. You have a video. Yes,
вам о чём-то говорит при Мак ты видео
this train is Masik.
Дава этого поезда Масик
I am looking for a
Это я ищ
video. It will be a sensation now. Yes, the channel will have a
видео сейчас будет да сейчас канал будет
million subscribers now.
миллион подписчиков
You will have a million. BT will be
тепер у тебя миллион БТ будет
TE 500 LRN. It
ТЕ 500 лрну
will be a sensation now, people. We are so
сейчас будет блин народ Вот это нам
lucky now.
фартануло
loads I
сечас грузит я
found a
нашёл
brother with a
брат с
weapon And what were they carrying there while the intrigue
оружием А что там везли пока интригу
Highmore was being carried am what
хаймор везли ам что
not to you you then in my opinion there
не вам у вас тогда такого по-моему не
was nothing like that what what were they
было ничего что что что
carrying And the most important thing for whom they were
везли И самое главное для кого
carrying a bunch of weapons to the station with
везли на вокзал куча оружия
their intrigue come on already video You found it I
своей интригой давай уже видос Ты же
can send you a link
нашл могу тебе ссылку скинуть
Gru I mean it doesn't load you cut off
Гру В смысле не грузит ты среза
no no you tell me
уже не не ты
those dreams you are taking a [ __ ] right now if
мне те сну это ты сечас сре сейчас срешь
you tell me tenu here give me the
если мне скажеш тену вот сюда сдай
link I'll open it for myself now here
ссылку Я сейчас себе открою тут
let's see for yourself that you are a swine
давай сам види что ты сва
but it turns out I went to the site with the article
но я получается сошл на сайт со статьёй
and here is a link to this video
и вот меня ссылочка на этот видосик есть
on YouTube Yes give me the link So you watched
на YouTube Да давай ссылку Так ты сам
the video yourself
видосик
I can't watch it now
посмотрел я я не могу сейчас посмотреть
Wait
Подожди
toty In this video you don't see any
тоты На этом видосе не видишь никакого
weapons and you say that there is something there now it's
оружия и рассказываешь что там сейчас
not clear
есть не понятно
what
что пока
this video is for now
это видео
Yes this is this specific video I haven't
Да это это конкретно видео Я не
seen that is you are now sending me a
видел то есть ты мне сейчас скидываешь
link to a video that you yourself haven't seen yes it
ссылку на видео которое ты сам не видел
turns out so what next
да получается так и что дальше
Oh what's in that video VM what  problem
О а что в том видео ВМ в чём проблема а
what's in that
что в том
video in short throw them here Yes,
видео короче те сюда скинуть Да ски же
come on just tell me what's in that video
давай просто расскажи что в том видео
that you haven't
кото ты не
seen
видел
so let's
так давайте бь вручную
write it manually like this
напишу так
Copy So I'm sitting in chat roulette from my phone
Скопируй Так я с телефона сижу в чат
as I'm copying it to you now the
рулетки как я тебе сейчас копирую
manicure is
маникюр
cool thank you filing it myself No I'm
классный спасибо подпиливание сам Нет
just cutting my hair and what kind of
просто стригу
varnish do you use
а а лак какой используешь
varnish Well do you think I use varnish
лак Ну ты думаешь я лак использую
you're a professional not just you have
ты профессионал не просто у тебя
some kind of feminine such delicate
какие-то женские такие нежные
fingers feminine delicate fingers They are my
пальцы женские нежные пальцы Они у меня
pianist's fingers they are feminine and a pianist
пальцы пианиста они женские а пианист
understood pianist pianist
понял пианист
damn it's just generally for the
пианист блин это просто вообще для
plot of an artistic Pianist at 19 years old
сюжета художественного Пианист в 19 лет
comes out in February to
выходит в феврале на
Simferopol just finger pi so Pani
Симферопольский просто пальц пи так Пани
so guitar
так гитари
Damn you're taking so long to type
Блин ты так долго набираешь
Well if you need to throw chat roulette
Ну если тебе нужно чат рулетку скидывать
I'm throwing you chat roulette you don't
я тебе скидываю чат-рулетку ты же мне не
want to throw it to me you're taking so
хочешь скинуть
long to type
с долго набираешь
So you take it on your phone and press copy
Так ты возьми на телефоне скопировать
And here press paste
нажми А тут нажми
I'm entering a link from the computer now
вставить я те с компьютера сейчас ввожу
as I'll copy it into the air from the computer
ссылку как я те воздуху скопирую компа
to  phone you are a Streamer
на телефон ты Стример
Exactly you are already nervous I
Точно ты уже нервничаешь мне это
like it Well, so you me with yours Come on,
нравится Ну так ты меня со своими Давай
come on, now you want to accidentally
давай ты сейчас ты хочешь случайно
press something with your finger just to
что-то пальцем нажать просто чтобы
switch like no
переключить типа нет
why have you almost finished writing now and
почему вот сейчас уже почти дописал
you have Telegram on your phone and on your
а у тебя есть Telegram на телефоне и на
computer on your computer and on your phone Yes Well,
компе на компе и на телефоне есть Да Ну
so you can
так ты в Telegram себе можешь
save a message in Telegram, drop a link on your
сохранённый сообщение скинуть ссылку на
phone and copy it to your
телефоне и скопировать на
computer you
компе
definitely couldn't say this before I'm manually taking it away,
точно не мог раньше сказать этот вручную
but don't wait if I can
те а не подожди если я ж получается
return the chat roulette now it will close me
сейчас верну чат рулетку то она меня
okay don't
ладно не
turn it off don't turn it
сворачивай не
off Here it comes
сворачивай Вот пришло
[laughter] It
[смех]
seems like this is a complete victory for now
Вроде это полная перемога пока
definitely the
точняк
21st century
XXI век
dude and ran away like psk it was
чувак и убежал лайк пска коце было
divine send it to all your friends Let
божественно скиньте всем своим знам
them see this real belt with
Пусть увидят этот реальный пояс с
weapons that a nineteen-year-old
оружием который девятнадцатилетний
teenager in Simferopol met that
подросток в Симферополе встречал что
letter on Instagram I don't know what it's for, what else,
пись на й Instagram Я не знаю для чого
look at it there
це тоб для чого ще тоб там дивитись на
y face But for you it's one two or
оцей й фейс Але для тебе це один два або
three clicks But you try me and I'll be to
три клика Але ты тримае мене и я буду к
Wow in me there are a bunch of fouls and in me there will be a
Вау в мене там Купа фолов и в мене буде
cool mood so that Robbie but cool video
класный настрий чтоб Роби но крут видео
letter on y Instagram Pok Andriy like
пись на й Instagram Пок Андрий вот
this come on I'm waiting for you
так давай я тебя чекаю